# Enas awad sello

= enas.awad169@gmail.com

© El-Sinbillawein El-Dkahlia

**L** +201020356669

linkedin.com/in/enas-sellow-36153219a/

# Summary

I graduated from Al-Azher university in 2017 then studied three diplomas in teaching and psychological health disabilities section, worked as an Arabic teacher for deaf and speechless,

I started my career in web devlopment with FWD frond-end track by the end of 2020,

I learned to code responsive webpages with (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ES6, Bootstrap, React).

I started UX design process in 2021 with google and coursera " Google UX Design Professional "

# Education

## ITI Deploma

· MEARN Stak (2022 Till now )

#### ITI Maharatech courses

- · Introduction to React JS (2022)
- · Database Fundamentals (2022)

#### web development courses

- One Million Arab Coders part of the Mohammed bin Rashid Global Initiatives (MBRGI) (2020)
- FWD & Udacity (2020 2021)
- Google growth UX Design Professional (2021 2022)

#### Self study at youTube

· Bootstrsp - git & github (2021)

# Psychological health Dibloma

- · Psychological health of disabilities (2019 2020) Kafr El-sheikh University
- · Abnormal physiology (2018 2019) Mansoura University

## General Diploma in Education

· Arabic teaching Diploma (2017 - 2018)

### alahzer university

· arabic and islamic studies for girl, Islamic Studies Department (2013-2017)

# **Work Experience**

#### Freelancer (20201 till now)

- · User Experience Designer
- · Frontend Developer

### Markting

- Admin for clothing salles group in Egypt and Saudi Arsbia at facbook(2021 till now)
- · American Council in Mansoura for several courses (2021)

## Customer Service (2020-2021)

· Al-Sllam medical company

#### Sales Manager (2018 -2020)

· Ramy kalil pharmacy

### Arabic Teacher

- · Middel school in Kafr El-sheikh
- · Elmentary school for deaf and speechles in El-mansoura

## skills

- Frontend Technologies [Html, Css(bootstrap), javaScript, ReactJs]
- SQL database
- · git&github
- UI/UX designing tools [figma, adobe XD]
- Arabic teacher

# languages

Arabic: Native English: good